[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is the result of 0.1 + 0.2 === 0.3?",
        "choice1": "true",
        "choice2": "false",
        "choice3": "",
        "choice4": "",
        "answer": 2,
        "category": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What does the escape sequence ‘\f’ stand for?",
        "choice1": "Floating numbers",
        "choice2": "Representation of functions that returns a value",
        "choice3": "Form feed",
        "choice4": "None of the above",
        "answer": 3,
        "category": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What does 'typeof typeof(null)' return?",
        "choice1": "Object",
        "choice2": "undefined",
        "choice3": "String",
        "choice4": "None of the above",
        "answer": 3,
        "category": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What does 'typeof(() => undefined) ' return?",
        "choice1": "Object",
        "choice2": "Function",
        "choice3": "undefined",
        "choice4": "null",
        "answer": 2,
        "category": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What will console.log(!!{}) return in console?",
        "choice1": "undefined",
        "choice2": "!!{}",
        "choice3": "true",
        "choice4": "false",
        "answer": 3,
        "category": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a void element in HTML?",
        "choice1": "br",
        "choice2": "img",
        "choice3": "iframe",
        "choice4": "hr",
        "answer": 3,
        "category": "HTML"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which is incorrect regarding global attributes in HTML?",
        "choice1": "There are only 3 global attributes: id, class, and style",
        "choice2": "Global attributes can be used with all HTML elements",
        "choice3": "An HTML element can have the same name for an id and a class",
        "choice4": "Global attributes do not have broad support across browsers",
        "answer": 1,
        "category": "HTML"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which HTML element is used to display a scalar measurement within a range?",
        "choice1": "<range>",
        "choice2": "<meter>",
        "choice3": "<gauge>",
        "choice4": "<measure>",
        "answer": 2,
        "category": "HTML"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Text within <EM> … </EM> tag is displayed as ________",
        "choice1": "bold text",
        "choice2": "indented text",
        "choice3": "list text",
        "choice4": "italic text",
        "answer": 4,
        "category": "HTML"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is the correct HTML for making a text area?",
        "choice1": "<input type='textbox' />",
        "choice2": "<input type='textarea' />",
        "choice3": "<textarea>",
        "choice4": "<textbox>",
        "answer": 3,
        "category": "HTML"
    }
]